# Ariadna Vanegas-Rubio

Junior Front-End Developer

**EXPERIENCE** 

**MakeInspires** | Mamaroneck, New York | February 2022 – Present *STEM Instructor* 

- Implemented and curated curricula to enhance learning and retention of coding techniques and methodologies by 20%
- Facilitated hands-on coding exercises and projects, allowing students to apply their knowledge and develop practical skills in front-end development
- Prepared and delivered grade-appropriate presentations on STEM concepts, guiding students through interactive activities that fostered a fun and encouraging learning environment

**Mioym** | Rye Brook, New York | March 2023 – May 2023 *Software Engineer Intern* 

- Developed and implemented custom web scraping scripts using JavaScript, Node.js, and popular libraries/frameworks such as Puppeteer, Cheerio, and Axios, resulting in a significant increase of 23% in leads and generating over 6,000+ leads
- Utilized Postman to write and execute HTTP requests, handle responses, and validate API endpoints for seamless data retrieval
- Collaborated with team members to optimize and fine-tune scraping scripts for improved performance, efficiency, and scalability

**Generation Junior Full Stack Java Developer Program** | Remote | August 2022 – December 2022

Training Participant

- Participated in a 16-week, 460+ hour Junior Full Stack Java Developer program that emphasizes hands-on practical application
- Learned and deployed the technologies involved in creating full stack web applications with Java using Spring Boot Framework, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3
- o Implemented basic unit tests and deployed the application to Docker

**eTeam Inc** | Bronx, New York | July 2021 – August 2022 *Patient Care Associate* 

- $\circ~$  Maintained 700+ client records and utilized CRM to analyze patient data, thereby improving the delivery of medical care by 30%
- Communicated and collaborated with Charge Nurse and Nurse teams to provide care for patients via messaging system through an electronic health record system
- Cooperated with patients to quickly identify problems regarding appointments and medication and developed solutions

#### **EDUCATION**

**Florida International University** | Sweetwater, Florida B.S. in Recreation & Sport Management

**Generation USA** | Remote | December 2022

Eull Stook Java Davalonas Cartification

(347)340-5215 ariadna.vanegas@gmail.com Bronx, New York linkedin.com/in/avrubio/ github.com/avrubio avrubio.dev

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Passionate, technically proficient, detailoriented problem solver with 460+ training hours and experience developing full stack Java applications. Interested in attaining a career that will allow me to further enhance my skills in software development as well as highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

# W3Schools JavaScript Certification

November 2022 o HTML

 SOLID OOP Principles

CSSJavaScriptJava

DependenciesInjectionUnit Testing

SQLREST APIs

(JUnit, Mockito)

• Spring Data JPA

o Node.js

Spring Data 37 FSpring Security

SpringBootBootstrap

(JWT)

# **PROJECTS**

Bao Sing Se - Creator, Developer

- o Developed front-end with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Vanilla JS.
- Created Mobile Responsive User Experience with CSS Grids that allowed the user to view on any device screen size
- Implemented a fully working web application with the following layers: Persistence: MySQL Database. Backend: REST API with Java and Spring Boot.

## **OmniFood** - Developer

- Developed front-end user experience using vanilla JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3
- Allowed users to have a customized experience based on meal plans selected